It was the perfect honeymoon...until it began.
Just Married is a romance, comedy film directed by Shawn Levy.
Although Tom Leezak and Sarah McNerney come from different worlds, they are
both unexpectedly swept off their feet after their first meeting.
They quickly fall in love and plan to get married, despite
opposition from Sarah's uptight, rich family.
After their wedding, the happy couple sets off - with the highest of hopes and ideals about
love and marriage - on what they expect will be the perfect honeymoon in Italy.
Thanks to a relentless string of bad luck with one disaster after another, and an impromptu visit from Sarah's wealthy one-time
ex-lover Peter Prentiss, the newlyweds experience the honeymoon from hell that tests the limits of their young love.
Is it worth throwing away their love and marriage?
Tom Leezak, played by Ashton Kutcher.
Sarah McNerney, played by Brittany Murphy.
Peter Prentiss, played by Christian Kane.
Kyle, played by David Moscow.
Lauren McNerney, played by Monet Mazur.
Mr. McNerney, played by David Rasche.
Just Married is a 2003 romantic comedy film directed by Shawn Levy, written by Sam Harper, and stars Ashton Kutcher and Brittany Murphy as a young newlywed
couple from different social classes who take their honeymoon to Europe, where obstacles challenge their ability to sustain in marriage.
Released by 20th Century Fox on January 10, 2003, the film was
successful at the box office despite being critically panned.
The film explores themes of jealousy, france,
venice, italy, married couple, ex-lover.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.